

💿 🛮 Irpin, Ukraine

+38(099)79-55-763

gushcha.olena@gmail.com

in Olena Korotenko

Languages

- English / Intermediate
- Ukrainian, Russian

Tools / Technologies

- Figma
- Adobe Ps, Ai, Ae, An
- Webflow
- Axure
- HTML5, CSS3, JS (jQuery)

Hard Skills

- Visual Communication
- Prototyping
- UX Research
- Responsive Design
- HTML/CSS/JS Coding

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Result/quality orientation
- Planning and organizing
- Quick thinking/learning
- Personal motivation
- Empathy & Communication

Olena Korotenko

Be Banana Hammock

looking for remote job

UX/UI designer, web designer

Profile

A goal-oriented accomplished UX/UI designer with strong knowledge of HTML5/CSS3/JS(jQuery) coding and with over 6 years of experience that by the use of creativity, teamwork, and result/quality orientation can solve complex problems and make a positive impact on your company.

Job experience

Web designer / CM Network A/S

Mrch 2018 - Oct 2021

Denmark

Complete development of advertising landing and promo pages - UI design and HTML5/CSS3/JS(jQuery) coding. Creating animation by using CSS3. Creating banners for campaings. Graphic design of posters for articles of the Jofibo site.

Junior Front-End Developer / Edipresse Media

Aug 2015 - Mrch 2018

Sept 2014 - Oct 2019

Kuiv, Ukraine

Front-end development of advertising landing and promo pages - HTML5/CSS3/ JS(jQuery) coding. Creating animated banners.

Lecturer / National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Kuiv, Ukraine

The Academic Degree of Doctor of Philosophy (Candidate of Engineering Sciences) in the field of polygraphy was obtained. Teaching the subjects "Web design", "UX/UI design", "Security printing".

Education

UI/UX Design Pro Courses

Febr 2022

Kuiv, Ukraine, Hillel IT School

Prog.kiev.ua, ITDVN, Udemy, Coursera, Skill Up, Front-End Developer courses

2016-now

online learning

High education

The Academic Degree of Doctor of Philosophy (Candidate of Engineering Sciences) in the field of polygraphy

Febr 2018

Kuiv, Ukraine, National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

The Master Degree in the field of Printing Technologies

Kuiv, Ukraine, National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

The Master Degree in the field of Finance and Credit

Jun 2013

Jun 2014

Kuiv, Ukraine, National aviation university